■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
以下事件发生在 早晨8点到9点之间
The following takes place between 8:00 AM and 9:00 AM.
事件实时发生
Events occur in real time.
把手机收起来
Put the phone away.
就一分钟
Uh, one more minute.
你五分钟之前就这么说的
That's what you said five minutes ago.
-爸爸  -宝贝
Dad... I got you the phone
手机是让你有急事时用的
For emergencies, honey.
这就是急事啊
Well, this is an emergency.
好吧
Fine.
等等  那你怎么就可以用电话
Wait, now, how come you get to talk on the phone?
这不公平
That's not fair.
生活总是不公平的
Life's not fair.
喂
Hello.
Hello?
哪位
Who is this?
艾米丽
Emily?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
行动  快
Go! move!
行动
Take it.
所有人趴下
Everybody down!
爸爸  爸爸
Dad... dad...
爸爸
Dad...
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! dad!
艾米丽
Emily!
-艾米丽  -爸爸
Dad! dad! Emily!
爸爸
Dad!
艾米丽  艾米丽
Emily! Emily!
快点  进去
Go! get in there!
-爸爸  -我们走
We gonna go.
我们走
Let's go!
请不要伤害我女儿
Please don't hurt my daughter.
我有钱
I've got money.
我们不要你的钱  拉森先生
We don't want your money, Mr.Latham.
我们只想让你帮我们修点东西
We just need you to fix something for us.
按时间表  今天是第三天的
For the record chart, this is the third day
参议员听证会
Of this senate hearing
调查最近被撤销的反恐小组
Investigating human rights violations
暴力侵权的案件
By the recently disbanded Counter Terrorist Unit.
昨天当我们休庭的时候
Yesterday, when we adjourned,
我们讨论过反恐小组探员
We were discussing brutality and torture
行动过程中的野蛮行径和刑讯逼供
By CTU agents in the course of their operations.
证人  请亮明身份
Will the witness please state his name?
杰克·鲍尔
Jack Bauer.
鲍尔先生  我没看到你的律师到场
Mr.Bauer. I don't see your counsel present.
他或她不知道我们要开始了吗
Is he or she not aware that we're about to start?
我已经选择不要律师
I've chosen not to retain counsel.
鲍尔先生  我得提醒你
Mr.Bauer, I have to advise you
我们要呈现在你面前
That many of the questions
诸多事件的法律性质
That we're about to appose to you are of a legal nature
所导致的后果  可能会对你不利
might result in answers that could incriminate you.
这个我懂  参议员
I understand that, senator.
我们可以把你的出证时间推迟到下午
We can postpone your testimony until this afternoon
如果你想找个律师的话
If you'd like to bring in representation
这也是我强烈建议的
Something that I would strongly advise.
第一个问题是什么  参议员
What is the first question, senator?
那好吧
All right, then.
我们开始
Let's begin.
鲍尔先生  亚伯拉罕·哈达德是什么人
Mr.Bauer. Who is Abraham Haddad?
这是机密
That information is classified.
我们代表全美国的民众
We represent the people of the united states,
把这些文件列为非机密了
and we have declassified those files on their behalf.
现在我再问你一次
Now I'm going to ask you one more time.
亚伯拉罕·哈达德是什么人
Who is Abraham Haddad?
他曾经是恐怖组织间谍中的一员
He was a member of the terrorist sleeper cell.
2002年反恐小组开始对其监控
CTU had him under surveillance in 2002.
你是否在没履行程序的情况下
And is it true that you detained Mr.Haddad
就扣留了哈达德先生
Without due process,
并对他使用过
And that you used
极端的审讯手段
Extreme interrogation methods on him
直至他回答了你的问题
Until he answered your questions?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
你承认在审讯期间
Would you say that you broke procedure
破坏了程序吗
With this interrogation?
也许吧
Probably.
Probably?
好一个轻描淡写的回答
Well, that's a... very cavalier answer.
看来你对你的行为并无悔意
You don't seem to care about the implications here.
你的回答是什么  鲍尔先生
Well, Mr. Bauer?
对不起  参议员
I'm sorry, senator.
我没明白你的问题
I didn't hear a question.
那好
All right, then.
你是否虐待过哈达德先生
Did you torture Mr. Haddad?
如果按照日内瓦公约
According to the definitions
的定义来说
Set forth by the geneva convention,
是的
Yes, I did.
参议员  让我猜猜你的想法
Senator, why don't I save you some time.
你是想借此牵连反恐小组
It's obvious that your agenda is to discredit CTU
然后酝酿出一套理论来
And generate a series of indictments...
我唯一的目的就是找出真相
My only agenda is to get to the truth.
我不这么认为  先生
I don't think it is, sir.
你说什么
Excuse me?
亚伯拉罕·哈达德计划袭击载有45人的客车
Abraham Haddad had targeted a bus carrying 45 people,
其中有10名乘客是儿童
Ten of which were children.
参议员  事实是我成功阻止了这次袭击
The truth, senator, is I stopped that attack from happening.
通过严刑拷打哈达德这种手段
By torturing Mr. haddad.
通过使用我认为必要的手段
By doing what I deem necessary
来保护无辜的生命
to protect innocent lives.
因此鲍尔先生  你的理论就是
So basically what you are saying, Mr. Bauer,
为达目的不择手段
is that the ends justified the means，
并且可以凌驾于法律之上
and that you are above the law.
每次我临危受命
When I am activated,
介入调查  都只有一个目的
When I am brought into a situation, there is a reason.
目的就是要不惜一切代价
And that reason is to complete the objectives
完成任务
Of my mission at all costs.
即便是要违反法律吗
Even if it means breaking the law?
对于战士来说
For a combat soldier,
成败的关键就在于
The difference between success and failure
能否因敌制宜
Is your ability to adapt to your enemy.
我的敌人
The people that I deal with,
他们不在乎你的规则
they don't care about your rules.
他们只在乎结果
All they care about is a result.
我的使命就是 阻止他们达到目的
My job is to stop them from accomplishing their objectives.
我只是以其人之道还治其人之身
I simply adapted.
对于您的问题
In answer to your question,
我是否凌驾于法律之上
Am I above the law?
回答是  是的
No, sir.
我更乐于被 您所代表的广大人民来评判
I am more than willing to be judged By the people you claim to represent.
并由他们来决定我的命运
I will let them decide what price I should pay.
但请你别坐那儿摆出一副同情的样子
But please do not sit there with that smug look on your face
还期待我会为自己所做的决定而后悔
And expect me to regret the decisions that I have made,
而事实是
Because, sir, the truth is,
我不后悔
I don't.
打扰一下  先生
Excuse me, sir.
抱歉打扰了  参议员先生
Sorry for interrupting, senator.
我是联邦调查局的蕾妮·沃克
I'm Renee Walker with the FBI.
这有一张杰克·鲍尔的传票
We've a subpena for Jack Bauer.
我需要您立即 将他转交于我羁押
I need him remanded Into my custody immediately.
我对你的传票
I'm not surprised that anyone has a subpoena
并不怀疑
Mr. Bauer, but right now,
但你现在只能等着
You're going to have to wait your turn.
他正在接受美国参议院的审问
He's being questioned by the united states senate.
先生  我们现在就需要鲍尔先生
Sir, we need Mr. Bauer immediately.
看来  我们只能放你走了
Well, apparently we're going to have to let you go
暂时离开
For now,
但对你的审讯还没结束
But we're not done with you.
我们明早
We'll reconvene with you
同一时间继续
Tomorrow morning at the same time.
你明白吗
Is that understood?
明白
Yes, sir.
你可以跟这些探员走了
All right. then you go along with these agents.
我们继续
Well, let's proceed.
警卫  传唤下一位证人
Bailiff, call the next witness.
这是怎么回事
What is this about?
鲍尔先生  我是沃克探员
Mr. Bauer, I'm special agent walker,
这位是泰勒探员
this is agent Tyler.
我需要你随我们去一趟办公室
We need you to come with us to our office.
就在街口不远处
It's just down the block.
到了就会告诉你的
You'll be briefed when we get there.
你好
Hello?
詹尼斯  是我  拉里在哪
Janis, it's me. where's Larry?
他在给多曼的小组做简报
He's briefing Dornan's group.
告诉他我接到鲍尔了  我们马上出发
Tell him I got Bauer. We are leaving here now.
那太好了  不过情况又恶化了
Oh, that's good cause the situation is heating up.
怎么了
What are you talking about?
我们追踪的那伙人
That crew we've been tracking?
他们刚刚绑架了一个叫迈克尔·拉森
They just grabbed a man named Michael Latham.
拉森  他是国安局防火墙系统的工作人员
Latham? he worked on homeland's firewall project.
他可不只是个员工
Oh, he didn't just work on it, he designed it.
他不仅在那工作  而且设计了这个系统
He's the chief engineer of the government's
他是政府基础设施安全体系的首席工程师
Infrastructure security system.
好吧  我马上到
All right, I'll be there soon.
你帮鲍尔取消安检了吗
Did you get Bauer cleared through security yet?
-还没呢  -蕾妮正他带过来
Not yet. well, Renee's bringing him in.
几分钟后就到了
There's only a couple of minutes out.
几分钟可搞不定
Then you won't need him cleared for a couple of minutes.
肖恩  作为朋友  我想给你一些
Shawn, as a friend, I'd like to give you some...
你不是我的朋友
You're not my friend.
好吧  作为一个将要成为
Sure. as someone is close to a friend
你的朋友的人  想给你点建议
that you are ever going to get, let me give you some advice.
大多数人都不喜欢被挖苦
Most people don't like sarcasm.
我倒是不介意  因为我很开朗
I myself have no problem with it, 'cause I'm cheerful.
我是个乐观的人
I'm a cheerful person.
你是一个乐观的人吗
You're a cheerful person?
快点帮鲍尔取消安检
Just get Bauer cleared.
在过去的八周
For the past eight weeks,
这家事务所一直在调查
This office has been investigating
一系列的技术盗窃案
a series Of technology thefts
关于软件  用户门阵列芯片和神经网络
Software, custom gate array chips, neural networks.
鉴证科推断这次入侵
Forensics concluded that the break-ins
是同一伙人干的
were the work of the same crew,
但我们不知道他们何时罢休
But we didn't know what their end game was
直到目前
Until now.
这是迈克尔·拉森
This is Michael Latham.
国家机密设施及
The chief engineer
防火墙工程的
On the classified infrastructure portal,
首席工程师
Homeland's firewall project.
十分钟前他被绑架了
He was abducted ten minutes ago
也是那个技术盗窃团伙干的
By the same group behind the technology thefts.
你认为他们正利用拉森
You think they're using this guy latham
-来突破CIP防火墙吗  -那正是我担心的
To get through the cip firewall? That's I concerned.
他们偷盗的设备正好可以被用来
The hardware they stole could be used
制作突破防火墙的装置
To build a device to do just that.
而拉森正是能做到的几个人之一
and Latham is one of the few people that can do it.
我们猜想他正被迫制作此装置
We assume he's being forced to work on the device,
或者他已经死了
Or that he's already dead.
打扰一下  蕾妮把杰克·鲍尔带来了
Excuse me. Renee is on the way in with Jack Bauer.
谢谢  我们叫大家来
Thank you. we've tasked
是为了协助调查
Your people to help this investigation.
看起来肖恩已经查到信息了
Seem Shawn he has got the packets.
开始行动吧
We're on it.
我们已经接入GSA117航班了
We are online with GSA 117.
有多少个系统
How many systems?
通信系统  导航系统
Communications, navigation...
但我们还需要控制其他的系统
But we need the other systems working.
去看下拉森的进展
Check on Latham.
好了  完成了
All right... it's done.
东北三号塔台
Northeast three,
我是GSA117号航班
This is global skies 117.
请求起飞
We are ready for clearance.
GSA117  收到
GSA 117, roger.
资料显示  你们将飞往肯尼迪国际机场
You are clear to JFK airport as files.
保持飞行高度5000
Maintain 5,000.
起飞10分钟后
Expect flight level of 280
进入飞行高度280
Ten minutes after departure.
收到  肯尼迪国际机场  飞行高度280
Clear to JFK, expect flight level 280.
欢迎乘坐环球航空117航班
Welcome to global skies flight No.117,
本次旅程从里根国际机场飞往肯尼迪国际机场
Passenger service from Reagan National to JFK.
纽约的天气为多云
Weather in new york is cloudy
可能会伴有雷雨出现
with a chance Of thunder showers,
所以旅程中我们可能会遇到乱流
so we may run into some turbulence along the way.
这里是塔楼  等待杜勒斯机场清空跑道
Tower to skies, awaiting traffic off of Dulles.
GSA117号航班  请保持你的位置
Position hold, GSA 117.
GSA117号航班收到
Gsa 117, that's correct.
鲍尔先生
Mr. Bauer
我是梅杰·拉里·莫斯  这的负责人
Major Larry Moss, I'm the head of this office
请你来这
You're here
是因为沃克探员认为你或许
Because agent walker thinks
能协助我们进行调查
You might be able to help us with the investigation.
就个人而言
Now, personally,
我深表怀疑
I have my doubts,
希望你能证明我是错的
But I'll be happy to be proven wrong.
我很庆幸我不是来应聘的  莫斯探员
Well, lucky for me, I'm not here to apply for a job, agent moss.
就个人而言  我不在乎你高兴与否
Personally, I don't care what makes you happy,
所以让我们早点结束吧
So let's get this over with.
带他去蕾妮的办公室
Take him to Renee's office.
需要我和你一起吗
You want me in the room with you?
不了
No.
蕾妮
Renee...
你看过他的档案
You've read his file.
你一不小心说错话
Bauer's the kind of guy
鲍尔这人就会发飙
You say the wrong thing, he can go off.
放心吧  拉里
I'll be fine, larry.
要是他发飙了  我会叫你的
If he goes off, I'll call you.
好吧  要是没什么进展
All right, but if he doesn't produce,
别浪费时间
Don't waste our time.
把他送回去
Throw him back.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
鲍尔先生  我们有一个紧急国家安全事务
Mr Bauer, we have a national security matter
需要立即处理
that has gone critical.
希望你能帮我们
I'm hoping you can help us with it.
请坐
Please sit down.
我把信息发给国土安全局了
I sent the differentials to Homeland.
还有什么
Was there anything else
需要我做的吗
You needed me to do?
没了
No.
鲍尔已经被起诉了吗
Has Bauer been indicted yet?
还没  不过参议院听证会后就要开始
No, but he will be after the senate hearings.
CIP防火墙保护着我国所有的基础设施系统
The CIP firewall protects every major infrastructure system
要是它被破解了
In this country. If it were breached,
电信业  交通运输业  电力系统
Telecommunication, transportation, power grids
都将处于危险之中
They would all be vulnerable.
沃克探员  对吧
Agnet Walker right?
是的
Yes.
我已经离职了
I'm not active.
司法部要对我提起刑事诉讼
The DOJ is about to file criminal charges against me.
对于你现在的情况
I'm not exactly in a position
我是爱莫能助
to help you with your situation.
尽管我知道事态严峻
As much as I understand how dire it is...
不  我认为你不了解
No, I don't think you do.
这次危机的幕后主使之一
One of the men behind this threat
是你的一个老熟人
is someone you know.
这不可能
That's not possible.
托尼·阿尔梅达已经死了
Tony Almedia is dead.
很明显  他没死
Apparently not.
他就死在了我的面前
I was there when he died.
几分钟后他就被送去急救了
And he was rushed away by the EMTs a minute later.
从那以后你就再没见过他
You never saw him after that
而几小时后
and hours later
你就被中国政府带走了
You were abducted by the chinese government.
不
No.
不可能
要是托尼还活着  我一定会知道的
If Tony were still alive, I would know.
他会跟我联系的
He will contact me.
我们从盗窃案发生地点的
We recovered this image from a security camera
一个摄像机中恢复了这张图片
Where one of the technology thefts took place.
有时间和日期的标注
It's time stamped and dated.
图像可能是伪造的
Images can be manipulated.
这张肯定不是
Not this one.
抱歉  我不相信
I'm sorry, I don't believe it.
我挖开了阿尔梅达的坟墓
I had Almedia's grave exhumed.
DNA检验证明
DNA test confirmed that
里面埋的不是他的尸体
it was not his body that was buried.
证据就在这里
The evidence is right here.
要是你对它视而不见
If you want to leave
就这么走的话  随便你
without looking at it, go ahead.
GSA117号航班上路了
GSA117 on the road.
马斯特斯
Masters?
在  长官
Yes, sir.
我们进入他们系统了
We are in their system
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
收到  塔台  GSA117  转向飞往高度126.8
Roger tower, GSA 117, switching to departure 126.8.
旅途愉快
Have a good day.
出什么问题了
What's the problem?
CIP模块不工作了
The CIP module stoped working.
不工作了  什么意思
What do you mean it stopped?
它相位失调了
It keeps going out of phase.
拉森不是说没问题了吗
I thought Latham said it was good to go.
可是  还有问题
Well, it's not.
好吧  拿给我
All right, let me have it.
你动什么手脚了
So what did you do?
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything.
我发誓
I swear.
那为什么它不工作了
Then why isn't it working?
我不知道
I don't know.
修好它
Fix it.
马上
Now.
你最好再快一点
You're gonna want to move faster than that.
几分钟内
See, 'cause if you can't make this work
要是你修不好
In the next few minutes,
我就不需要你了
I won't need you anymore.
懂我的意思吗
You understand what that means?
很好
Good.
修好它
Now fix it.
官方估计大约有30万平民
Officials say that an estimated 300,000 civilians
男人  女人和儿童
Men, women, and children--
都在本杰明·朱玛将军的种族清洗中
Have been killed as part of general Benjamin Juma's
惨遭杀害
Campaign of ethnic cleansing.
位于非洲的桑加拉的幸存者
Survivors in the African nation of Sangala,
相信美方进行干涉
Believe American intervention
以避免更多的伤亡是必要的
Is necessary to prevent further bloodshed.
目前白宫还未对此事公开表态
The white house has made no public statements...
朱玛是自卢旺达大屠杀后
Juma's perpetrating the worst mass murder
又一非洲暴君
Africa has seen since rwanda.
但如果你读报上的专栏评论
But if you read the columns...
我知道
I do.
半数人反对我们采取行动
Half of them are against our taking action.
但如果我们无动于衷
But if we don't...
六个月以后  这帮人又会
Six months from now, those same members of the press
出来指责我们道德沦丧
Will be accusing us of moral bankruptcy.
我们可以重新考虑通过联合国采取行动
We can always revisit the un option.
伊桑  联合国已形同虚设
The UN's paralyzed, ethan,
眼睁睁看着那个疯子屠杀民众
While people are being butchered by that madman.
我们必须担起责任来
We have to lead.
即便是我们单枪匹马也再所不惜
Even if it means going it alone.
我不会昧着良心眼睁睁看着
I'm not gonna have hundreds
这么多无辜生命受难
Of thousands of lives on my conscience.
朱玛将军
General Juma
-必须被铲除  -只要您一声令下
-has to be stopped. - He will be,
总统阁下
Madame president.
这事不难
As soon as you give the order.
参谋长联席会议的人都到齐了吗
Are the joint chiefs here yet?
他们都在战略情报室
They're gathering in the situation room.
准备好后他们会通知我们的
They'll call as soon as they're ready for you.
我刚听说
I just heard
凯文·奥德里奇又在CNB上大放厥词了
Kevin Aldrich is doing a piece for CNB.
他还在利用媒体施压
He's still pressing his case
反对我们出兵
Against sending our troops in.
他嫌我们的麻烦还不够多吗
As if getting through this day won't be hard enough.
如果您同意  我可以坐下来同他谈谈
If you want, I can sit down with him
让他三思而后行  他就在媒体接待室
And try to get him to hold off; he's in the press room.
我不觉得这是个好主意  亨利
I'm not sure that's a good idea, Henry.
你现在完全没必要这么做
This is the last thing you need right now,
尤其正当舆论界争执不下之时
Especially with public opinion so split.
如果你觉得你能说服他  就去做吧
If you think you can talk Aldrich down, do it.
总统阁下
Madame president,
参谋长联席会议可以开始了
The joint chiefs are ready.
这是为您准备的简报
Here's your briefing package.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
你行的
Good luck.
材料都在这了吗
Is this everything?
是的
It's all there.
恕我多嘴
I don't mean to sound like a broken record,
但我怀疑您丈夫能否
But I'm not sure your husband is up
说服得了奥德里奇
To handling Aldrich.
他可以的
Henry's fine.
我得承认他比过去好多了  但...
He's better, I realize that, but...
他需要更多的时间
It's going to take more than a few months.
从丧子之痛中挣脱出来
He lost a son.
您不也是吗
So did you.
可您没让悲痛
And you haven't let your loss interfere
影响工作
With your job.
您丈夫是个坚强的人
Your husband is a strong man,
但他没像您那样想得开
But he doesn't have your resilience.
这不是想不想得开的问题  伊桑
It's not a matter of resilience, Ethan.
我无时无刻
There's not a day that goes by,
不在怀念我的儿子
Not a moment when I don't think about my son.
但我们现在马上要开战了
But I'm about to take this nation to war
悲伤对我来说太奢侈了  我承受不起
And grief is a luxury I can't afford right now.
在会议开始之前
Before we begin,
首先我想感谢诸位
Let me thank each of you for the time
为此付出的辛勤工作
And work you've put into this operation.
将我们的士兵送上前线
Putting American lives at risk
是我一生中
Is the hardest decision
最难的抉择
I've ever had to make...
但我已别无选择
But it is one that has to be made.
怎么样了
What was that?
修好了
It's working.
-刚才为什么坏了  -仪器过热了
- What was wrong? - it was overheating.
我找到了一个解决办法
I came up with a workaround.
试一下
Try it now.
好了
There. yeah.
现在又可以正常
It's transmitting again.
收发数据了
We can send and receive.
AA-123号航班
Double a-123
请保持航线
Maintain course.
这是怎么回事
What was that?
我这边也是
I just got it, too.
你们也失去同步信号了吗
Did you guys lose synch?
我刚才也是  不过现在好了
I did, but we're back up now.
还有人出问题吗
Anybody else lose synch?
-我这边没事  -一切正常
- No, I'm fine. - No, I'm good.
一切正常
I'm fine.
出什么事了
What's going on?
这听起来有点不可思议
This is gonna sound crazy,
但我们三个的屏幕刚才晃动了一阵
But the three of us just got bumped for a second.
但纪录显示电压没有异常
But the log file doesn't show a power surge.
故障来自系统内部
This came from the system kernel.
这不可能
What are you talking about?
系统内部受严密保护
The kernel's protected.
让我查一下
Let me have a look.
我们现在唯一能确定的是托尼·阿尔梅达
All we know for sure is that Almeida is part of a homegrown
伙同国内恐怖分子意图破坏基础设施
Terrorist group that's targeting our infrastructure.
请你查证一下所有联邦特工机构
He could be working undercover,
看看他是不是在当卧底
Some kind of sting operation. you need
-执行绝密行动  -我们已经查证了
- To check every federal agency-- we have.
全国各地所有的部门机构
他不是我们的卧底
Almeida's not working for any of them.
他这么做一定另有隐衷
Then there must be some other explanation.
没错
Yeah, there is.
她的老婆被罗根总统
His wife was brutally murdered
指派的政府部门的特工
By a faction operating inside the government,
残酷杀害
Led by the president himself.
参与那次行动的人要么在蹲大牢
Everybody involved in that is either in prison
要么早被杀掉了
Or has been killed.
罗根总统根本没受到实质性的惩罚
The government gave president logan a slap on the wrist,
政府和他达成了协议
They cut him a deal.
只是把他软禁在
Sentencing him to house arrest
一个100英亩大的大农场里而已
On a hundred-acre ranch...?
你认为托尼会为了讨个公道
And you think Tony's looking for justice
而去报复这个国家吗
By attacking this country?
阿尔梅达已经一无所有
Almeida lost everything he had,
他完全有理由怪罪
And he's blaming it
这个他曾为之卖命的政府
On the government he spent his life serving.
你比我更能体会这种切肤之痛
But you'd know better than me how that feels...
以及他会怎样报复国家
...how far a man might go.
托尼决不至于走到那一步
Not that far.
他绝不会的
And not tony almeida.
这件事情一定有个合理的解释
There's a logical explanation for this.
只是你没看清而已
It's just something you're not seeing.
帮我找到阿尔梅达  一切就水落石出了
Help me find Almeida and you can ask him yourself.
你知道他是怎么想的
You know how he thinks.
你们接受过同样的训练
You had the same training.
你们这类人都彼此了解
You know the same people.
请授权我彻底查看你们所有
I'm going to need complete access
关于此事的原始资料
To all of your source material-- everything you've got on this.
请讲
Yes?
蕾妮  过来一下  这有新情况
Renee, come out here. something just came in.
马上就到
Be right there.
所有关于阿尔梅达团伙的资料都在这目录里
Everything we have on Almeida's crew is in this directory.
从这里入手... 我马上回来
Start here... I'll be right back.
出什么事了
What's going on?
东北航空交通管制台刚刚报告
Northeast air traffic control just called.
他们认为通讯系统
They reported a possible intrusion
不久前有可能
Into their communication systems.
-遭到了入侵  -找出是谁干的了吗
- It just happened. - can they source them?
他们正在试  但是目前仍一无所获
They're trying, but so far, nothing.
为什么你认为这事和阿尔梅达一伙有关
Why do we think this has to do with Almeida's crew?
我觉得这样的入侵
I don't think you get intrusions like this
除非有人暗中操纵
Unless someone's driving it,
而唯一能操纵的途径只有突破CIP防火墙
And the only way to drive it is through the cip firewall.
所以他们要入侵航空交通管制系统
So they're going after air traffic control.
事情看来有些眉目了
That's what it looks like.
请帮我接通白宫
Put me through to the white house.
你准备在纽约转机吗
You doing a turnaround in New York?
不了  准备休息两天
Nope. got two days off.
准备去找我男朋友玩
I'm meeting my boyfriend in the city.
那敢情好
Oh, that'll be fun.
道尔刚告诉我会遇上坏天气
Well, Doug said we were going to hit some weather.
我需要技术人员来交叉比对资料
I'm going to need tech support to cross-reference your files.
我让分析师西恩·希林格帮你完成
You'll be working with one of my analysts, sean hillinger.
他会给你所有你需要的情报
He can get you whatever files you need
来帮助我们找到阿尔梅达
To help us find Almeida.
不错  他们提升警戒等级了吗
Good. they raise the threat level yet?
看来阿尔梅达一伙已对航管系统下手了
Yeah. we think Almeida's group got into air traffic control.
什么  不可能
What? that doesn't make sense.
我用不着你想破脑袋  杰克
I don't need you to figure it out, Jack.
帮我找到他就行
Just help me find him.
西恩  这是杰克·鲍尔
Sean, this is Jack Bauer.
他会和你一起研究阿尔梅达的资料
He's going to be working with the Almeida files.
给他所需的一切资料
Give him whatever he needs.
那和联邦航空局联系的活儿谁干
What about interfacing with FAA?
詹尼斯正和多曼的手下一起干呢
Janis is working with some of Dornan's people on that.
-你帮好杰克就行了  -好的
You just help Jack. Fine.
-我去登记  -谢谢
I'll check in. thanks.
你想看些什么资料呢
What do you want to see?
就从这次技术盗窃案开始吧
Let's start with the technology thefts.
一共有多少
How many were there?
6份
Six.
试着进行一次全面的资料比对
Let's run a comp on all of them.
好极了
Fantastic.
远征航母舰队
The expeditionary strike force
及其海军航空队已经就位
And its carrier air wing are now on scene.
这样一来我们有更大的把握取得先机
This gives us full spectrum dominance of the battle space.
你估计朱玛的武装力量
What kind of resistance are you anticipating
会有多大程度的抵抗
From Juma's military?
微乎其微
Minimal.
我们的空军将横扫任何防御体系
Our air strikes will take out whatever defenses they've got.
只待我军直捣黄龙了
We can expect an open path to Juma's front door.
很好
Good.
万事俱备  只需您的一声令下了
All we need to launch is a go order from you.
看过斯蒂芬的战后评估报告后
You'll get a green light as soon as I've gone over
我就会给你下命令
Secretary stevens' post-invasion report,
不过他还没给我
Which I'm still waiting for.
几分钟后就给你  总统阁下
I'll have it for you in a few minutes, ma'am.
有什么问题就说
Unless there's a problem you'd like to discuss.
总统阁下  我对本次行动所持的异议
Madame president, my objection to this operation isn't
对在座诸位已不是什么秘密了
A secret to anyone in this room.
出兵干涉地球另一边的内战
For us to be wading into the middle
对于我们来说...
Of another civil conflict halfway around the world...
别再无休止地争论下去了  乔
We're done debating this, Joe.
当本杰明·朱玛大肆屠杀20多万同胞时
The UN's been issuing reprimands and economic sanctions
联合国还在忙于下达
While Benjamin Juma has slaughtered
对其施加的经济制裁令
Over 200,000 of his own people.
如果我们不阻止他
That number will continue to grow
伤亡数字还会持续上升
If we don't stop him now.
如果你不愿支持我们
And if you can't get behind what we're doing,
我会换一个支持我的国务卿
I'll find a secretary of state who can.
但是  我受够了你的消极态度
But I am done with your handwringing.
对不起  总统阁下
Excuse me, madame president.
国土安全局的蒂姆·伍兹在外面候着呢
Tim Woods from homeland security is outside.
他有事要见你
He needs to see you on another matter.
让他等等不行吗
Can it wait?
不行啊  是急事
No, ma'am, it can't.
好吧
All right.
等我回来  我们继续
We'll continue when I return.
乔  希望我回来时报告已经做好了
And, Joe, I want that report in front of me when I get back.
什么事情
What is it?
我不知道详细情况
I don't have the details,
但事关我国有被入侵的潜在危机
But it involves a potential domestic breach.
蒂姆会跟我们解释的
Tim is here to fill us in.
总统阁下
Madame president.
蒂姆  长话短说  大家还等着开会呢
Tim, make this brief; the joint chiefs are waiting.
关于这起系列技术盗窃案
We've been working with the FBI the last eight weeks,
我们已和联邦调查局合作调查了近两月
Investigating a series of technology thefts.
直到今天我们才恍然大悟
We didn't understand the implications of this until today.
就是这同一伙人劫持了一个名叫
The same people behind these thefts abducted a man
迈克尔·拉森的人
Named Michael Latham.
他是负责国家重点基础设施
He's one of the chief engineers in charge
防火墙工程的首席工程师之一
of protecting critical infrastructure.
说说我们此刻面临的麻烦是什么吧
Now, tell me what we're dealing with.
联邦调查局认为他们强迫拉森
The FBI thinks these same people have forced Latham
制造了一种入侵CIP防火墙的装置
To create a device to hack through the CIP firewall.
在防火墙保护之下的是
The firewall protects
国家的能源 水电 交通运输
Energy, utilities, transportation...
我此行是因为联邦航空局报告说
I'm here because the FAA reported some irregularities
航管系统出现了一些异常
In their air traffic control system.
你是说商务航班正受到威胁
Are you saying commercial flights are in danger?
很有可能
Possibly.
要我下达禁飞令吗
Do I need to give the order to ground air traffic?
恐怕没那么容易
I'm afraid it's not that simple.
现在美国领空范围内
Right now, there are more than 3,000 flights
有3000多架飞机
Over the continental United States.
要让所有的飞机停飞最少要12个小时
To ground them all would take 12 hours, minimum,
这同时也会造成恐慌
And it could create a panic.
那你的建议呢
Then what do you recommend?
先不动声色地减少起飞的航班数量
Let us quietly decrease air traffic
同时让调查局继续暗中查找线索
While the bureau works their leads.
我们会确保向您进行实时汇报
We'll make sure you're briefed on a real-time basis.
我觉得事有蹊跷
I don't like the timing of this...
什么蹊跷
Timing?
这事和我们要插手桑加拉一事有关系吗
Could this be connected to our intervention in Sangala?
联邦调查局还没找到任何关联的地方
The FBI hasn't found any connection.
所有证据显示我们对付的是
All the evidence suggests that we're dealing
本国的恐怖分子集团
with a domestic terror group, homegrown,
是强烈的反政府狂热者
with a strong, anti-government bias.
根据你提到的这些线索...
And these leads you mentioned--
你们能否在他们造成任何
Do you think you'll be able to catch these people
实质性破坏之前逮捕他们呢
Before they do any real damage?
调查局已动用了所有人手展开行动
The bureau's got everyone on it, ma'am.
你并没有回答我的问题
You didn't answer my question.
是的  总统阁下
No, ma'am. I didn't.
当然  我不是说要宽恕朱诺的滔天罪行
Of course, I don't condone what Juma's doing over there.
全世界到处都存在种族纷争
But tribal wars are being fought all over the world.
但为什么不是介入泰国或马来西亚呢
Why not intervene in Thailand, Malaysia?
这不是种族纷争  凯文
This isn't a tribal war, Kevin.
这分明是种族屠杀
It's a genocide.
制止屠杀是作为超级大国的
Ending it is the moral obligation
我们所肩负的职责
Of a nation as powerful as ours.
理想倒是蛮崇高的
That's a lofty aspiration,
但是现实可要复杂多了
But the reality is a lot more complex.
总统介入此事是经深思熟虑的
The president's going into this with both eyes open.
铲除朱玛之后她如何能确定
How can she be sure the cycle of violence won't continue
事态会不再恶化呢
After Juma's been taken out?
也许为了维持和平...
Could be stuck there indefinitely...
我们会陷入无休止的战争泥潭中
Keeping the peace.
如果我提供你做一个总统
If I gave you an exclusive preview of the president's
战后预案的独家报道
Post-invasion plans,
你也许就会改变主意了
You might change your mind.
你想用专访来收买我吗
You're trying to bribe me with an exclusive?
我只是想让你高抬贵手行个方便
I'm trying to get you to give us some rope.
你想让我怎么做  不写了
What are you asking me to do, stop writing
还是写我不想写的
Or write what I don't believe?
悉听尊便
Either one would be fine with me.
长官  您有一个专线电话
Sir, you have a phone call on your private line.
失陪一下好吗  凯文
Could you excuse me for a moment, please, kevin.
是查克·托兰  长官
It's Chuck Toland, sir.
等一下
Wait.
查克  有什么发现吗
Chuck, did you find something?
是的  但别高兴得太早
I did, but don't get carried away.
这并没确证你对罗杰死因的推测
It doesn't confirm your theory about how Roger died.
而是另有蹊跷
But it is suspicious.
我洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
他的女朋友萨曼莎在罗杰自杀
His girlfriend samantha received a large
三天后收到了一大笔来自
Lump-sum deposit in an off-shore bank account
海外账户的汇款
About three days after Roger's suicide.
你是说他其实是被谋杀的
You mean his alleged suicide.
是的  长官
Right, sir.
这笔钱是从哪来的
Where did the money come from?
不知道  看起来是洗过的钱
I couldn't tell. it looks like it's been washed.
来路不明
There's no readily identifiable source.
那  这说明了什么吗
So... what does this mean?
这说明她突然多了40万美金
All it means is that she suddenly came into $400,000.
要是想查出更多东西
If we're going to find out anything more,
我就得亲自去跟她谈谈
I'm going to need to talk to her personally.
你希望我这么做吗
Is that how you want me to handle it?
不  如果她确实有所隐瞒
No. if she's got anything to hide,
她不会和私人侦探说的
She's not going to talk to a private investigator.
的确
I agree.
那你现在需要我怎么做呢
So how do you want me to proceed?
我会亲自出马和她谈
I'll talk to her myself.
她还在那家经纪公司吗
Is she still at that brokerage firm?
是的 斯隆奇志经纪公司
Yeah, uh, Sloane Kittridge.
很好
Good.
我和奥德里奇谈完后
I'm going to finish up here with Aldrich.
带我去一个地方
Then I need you to take me somewhere,
不要做记录
And keep it off the manifest.
我不想让任何人知道我们的去向
I don't want anyone to know where we're going.
-遵命  长官  -盖奇探员
Yes, sir. Agent Gedge.
在  长官
Yes, sir.
你觉得查克是在利用我  对吗
You think Chuck's taking advantage of me, don't you?
我觉得我不适合做任何评论
It's not my place to say that, sir.
我就是要听听你的想法
I'm asking you anyway.
警方和联邦调查局都在调查
Sir, the police and FBI have both investigated
你儿子的死因
Your son's death.
是的  我认为这个私人侦探就是在
And yes, I believe this PI could be exploiting
利用您的悲痛来中饱私囊
Your grief for personal gain.
他的所谓的线索都是无稽之谈
These so-called leads that he's generating have led nowhere.
我儿子是不会自杀的
My son didn't kill himself.
我坚信这一点
I'm sure of it.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
你能再查一下那个端口吗
Can you check that socket again, please?
联邦航空局有报告什么异常吗
Has FAA reported any more anomalies?
在那三个之后就没有了  可能只是个小故障
Not since the first three. maybe it was just a glitch?
很可能是侵入防火墙时
Or it could have been a ripple caused when they broke through
所引起的一次波纹干扰
The firewall and entered the system.
如果他们侵入了系统  我怎么会看不到呢
Well, if they're in the system, I can't see them,
我检查了所有的ELR端口
And I've checked every ELR socket.
继续找
Keep looking.
蕾妮
Renee...
会发生什么事
Uh, what's going to happen?
-你什么意思  -如果阿尔梅达侵入了防火墙
What do you mean? if Almeida has broken through the firewall
我们就完了  不是吗
Then we're screwed, right?
我是说  同水源污染和电力中断相比
I mean, crashing a couple planes is really nothing compared
弄下来几架飞机
To contaminating the water system
已经根本不算什么了
Or bringing down the power grid...
不要这么想  詹尼斯
Don't think about it, Janis.
继续工作吧
Just stay on task.
好吧
Okay, so...
我会保持冷静的  好吗
I will just stay calm, right?
很好
Yeah.
回到第二份
Pull up the second one.
你已经看过了
You already looked at it.
我需要再看一遍  回去
I want to look at it again, pull it up.
-有什么发现吗  -没有  我们还在
Have you found anything? no, we keep looking
一遍遍地翻看同样的六份鉴证科材料
At the same six forensic reports over and over.
你在找什么  杰克
What are you looking for, Jack?
-一个切入点  -他们有通行证
An entry point. they had access cards.
是的  但是没有报告表明有通行证被盗
Yeah, but no one reported their access cards stolen,
-意味着通行证是伪造的  -那么
Which means they were forged. so...?
这些通行证都有个人签名
These access cards have individual signatures,
几乎不可能被伪造
Making them almost impossible to forge.
只有几个人能办到
There's only a couple guys who can do it.
你能进入反恐小组的资料库吗
Can you access old ctu files?
没问题
Sure.
调出1999年8月代号为哈特勒斯的档案
Pull up August 1999. Hatteras.
-刚接到国土安全局的电话  -怎么说
Just got a call from homeland. and?
他们已经报告总统了
They briefed the president
但她还不打算发布禁飞令
But she's not ready to ground planes yet.
在这  哈特勒斯档案
Here you go. Hatteras file.
知道吗  你可以雇佣一个时薪14美元的
You know, you can hire a $14.00-an-hour
数据管理员来干这个活  根本用不着我
Data applications geek to do this; you don't need me.
我可没时间登广告
I wouldn't advertise that.
在这  加布里埃尔·谢克特
There he is-- Gabriel Schector.
他是谁
Who is he?
一个供应商
He was a supplier.
托尼和我常在他那买些逃税的东西
Tony and I used him to buy things off-book.
看他是否在你们的资料库里
See if he's in your database.
有了
Yeah. he's there.
他还在洛杉矶吗
Is he still in Los Angeles?
不  根据资料显示
No. according to this earmark,
他9个月前去了华盛顿
He came to dc nine weeks ago.
盗窃案一周后就发生了
The thefts started a week after that.
这就是你们要找的人
That's your guy.
-有地址吗  -他在市中心租了一个办公室
Do you have an address? he's subletting an office downtown--
内勒路1208号  630号套房
1208 Naylor Road, Suite 630.
很好  带上战术小组  把他带来
All right, put a field team together, pick him up.
我致电西蒙斯法官  申请逮捕令
I'll call judge Simons, have a warrant ready.
-这样行不通  -为什么
That's a mistake. why?
你们没有时间去履行程序
You don't have time to go through the motions
对于谢克特  你拿出逮捕令
With Schector-- you serve him with a warrant,
他会叫律师  尽可能地拖延时间
He'll call his lawyers, he'll stall as long as he needs.
那么  你的主意是什么  杰克
So, what's the alternative, Jack?
闯进去  严刑逼供  像你以前的做法
Break in and torture the guy, like you used to do?
这不就是你在参议院听证会所陈述的吗
Isn't that how you ended up in front of a senate sub-committee?
就是这样的过程吗
Oh, is this how it starts?
你一拳打在我脸上  勒住我的脖子
You get in my face, tighten your jaw,
如果我不合作
Then if I say something you don't like,
你就把我往墙上撞
You slam me against the wall.
你根本不知道我会做什么
You have no idea what I do.
上次你叫我来  要我帮你
And last time I checked, you subpoenaed me.
给你建议  我做了
You want my help, you want my advice, take it.
如果你不需要  那就算了
You don't, don't.
我不在乎
I don't care.
鲍尔先生  你说你曾经和谢克特共事过
Mr. Bauer... you said you used to work with this man schector.
他很了解你吗
How well does he know you?
非常了解
He knows me.
拉里  我能和你谈谈吗
Larry, can I talk to you for a second?
-我想让鲍尔和我一起去  -不行
I want to take Bauer with me. no.
想都别想  我不能让他对嫌犯动手
Forget it. I'm not letting him put his hands on a suspect.
他不需要这么做
He won't need to put his hands on anybody.
我猜如果他去  谢克特肯定会说的
My guess is if he's in the room, schector will talk.
蕾妮  你看见了他刚才的行为
Renee, you saw what he just...
我只想在情况恶化之前找到阿尔梅达
I'm trying to find Almeida before it's too late,
而谢克特是我们最好的线索
And Schector is our best lead.
你想和鲍尔同流合污吗
So you want to intimidate him with Bauer?
谢克特知道鲍尔的手段
Schector knows how far Bauer might go.
我们可以利用这一点
Let's use that.
好吧  要是谢克特不屈服呢  怎么办
Yeah, and if Schector doesn't blink, then what?
我会看住鲍尔的
I'll keep Bauer on a short leash.
蕾妮  我们是联邦调查局  不是反恐小组
Renee, we're the fbi, not ctu. we honor the law.
我们依法行事  即使事情很棘手
Even when it's not convenient.
拉里  情况正在逐渐恶化
Look, this situation is heating up fast, Larry.
现在总统也介入了
The president's into it now,
她希望得到结果
And she's expecting results.
是的  我明白了
Yeah, I know.
你来决定吧
It's your call.
但我向你保证  我会看住鲍尔
But I promise you, I can handle Bauer.
好吧
All right.
我让你来负责
But I'm holding you responsible.
我会派支援过去的
And I'm sending backup teams.
好的
Okay.
杰克
Jack.
你跟我走  按我说的做
You're coming with me, and you're doing this my way.
跟我说说谢克特
Tell me about Schector.
在他自己干之前  他在圣地亚哥干
Out of San Diego, till he went on his own.
合法的吗
Legitimate?
是的  刚开始是  后来他越来越贪婪
Yeah, at first, then he got greedy.
开始利用他的关系获取各种技术
Started using his connections to acquire
然后在黑市上贩卖
Technology, sell it on the gray market.
-他卖给谁  恐怖分子吗  -不
Who'd he sell to, terrorists? no.
通常是那些试着钻法律空子的外国政府
Usually foreign governments trying to get around treaties.
你和托尼是怎么认识他的
And how did you and Tony get involved with him?
他是个很好的情报来源
He was a great conduit for intel.
反恐小组不介意 你们和他的交易吗
CTU didn't mind that you Were letting this guy stay in business?
反恐小组根本不知道
CTU didn't know.
只有我和托尼知道
It was just Tony and me.
你和托尼关系很好吗
So you and Tony were tight?
是的
Yeah...
非常好
Yeah, we were close.
好吧  听起来像是这个
All right, so it sounds like Tony,
大家都认为死了的托尼
Who everyone thinks is dead,
计划了威胁美国安全的恐怖行动
Puts together a plan to hijack American security.
他找谢克特来帮助他实施计划
He contacts Schector to help him with this plan.
听起来是这样
Yeah.
看起来你还是不相信
Except you don't believe it.
托尼会这样做
That Tony's dirty.
我只相信托尼还活着
I believe that Tony's alive.
我觉得他是在铤而走险
And I believe he's doing something dangerous,
所以我们必须找到他
And that we need to find him.
已经确认谢克特在里面
We confirmed Schector's inside.
-你想怎么做  -我和鲍尔进去
How do you want to handle this? I'm going in with Bauer.
-你自己  -我想让谢克特开口
Alone? I want Schector to talk.
我不想吓到他  支援来了告诉我
I don't want to spook him. call me when backup gets here.
马托波的部队藏匿在
Matobo's fighters are hidden outside the capital
首都外围的三个营地中
In three camps.
一号  二号和三号
Alpha, beta and delta.
一旦空中打击完成
Our ground forces will join up with them
我们的地面部队会和他们交火
Once the air strikes are completed.
要确保瓦格纳将军实施
Make sure general Wagner understands
控制城市秩序的首要作战计划
Our priority is to maintain order in the streets.
民众想要看到的是
The people need to see that their
他们的国家是在法律的监管之下
Country's being governed under the rule of law.
要是马托波在没有审判的前提下
What happens when Matobo's men
就对朱玛将军进行处决  我们怎么办
Execute general Juma without a trial?
我们是插手  还是让他们自己解决
Should we intervene or let the mob tear them apart?
我一会就要和马托波先生会面
I'm meeting with Mr. Matobo
就在几分钟后
In a few minutes.
我会让他管好他的人
I'll make sure he keeps his men in line.
乔
And, Joe,
我很抱歉让你在众位参谋长
I was wrong to dress you down
面前很没面子
In front of the joint chiefs.
对不起
I'm sorry.
您无需道歉  总统阁下
No need to apologize, madame president.
您的压力太大了
You're under a lot of pressure.
这不是借口
That's still no excuse.
谢谢  我很感谢您这样说
Thank you, ma'am, I appreciate that.
但是如果你不能处理好这事
The fact remains, if you can't get behind this operation
我会要你辞职
With both shoulders, I will need your resignation.
请放心  总统阁下
That won't be necessary, ma'am.
无论我有什么疑问
Whatever doubts I have,
-我都会守口如瓶  -很好
I'll keep them to myself. good.
打扰了  总统阁下
Excuse me, madame president.
什么事  伊桑
What is it, Ethan?
我认为应该告诉您
I thought you'd want to know,
亨利和奥德里奇已经达成协议
Henry and Aldrich has agreed to delay his broadcast
将报道推迟24小时
For 24 hours.
亨利成功了
Henry's doing?
我  低估了他
I, uh, underestimated him.
让他介入是正确的
Letting him intervene was the right call.
这是个好消息
Well, that's some good news.
防火墙的情况怎么样了
What about the firewall situation?
联邦调查局有什么进展吗
Has the FBI made any progress?
他们已经找到了一个与之有关联的人
They've identified a man who may have information.
正准备审讯他
They're about to question him.
谢克特是不会轻易
It's more than likely
把消息告诉你的
Schector's not going to give you this information easily.
记住  这是联邦调查局的行动
Just remember, this is an FBI operation.
我们要依法行事
We work within the confines of the law.
你可以威胁他  但别对他动手
You can threaten him, but do not lay hands on him.
一旦我看到你越轨
The minute I see you crossing that line,
我就把你抓起来  明白吗
I will pull you back, understood?
明白
Understood.
沃克探员  联邦调查局
Agent Walker, FBI.
我要见加布里埃尔·谢克特
I'm here to talk to Gabriel Schector.
稍等
Just a second.
有什么我能效劳的吗
Can I help you?
杰克·鲍尔
Jack Bauer?
你好啊  加布里
How are you, Gabe?
你竟然加入联邦调查局了
Didn't know you were FBI.
我没有
I'm not.
只是顺便过来看看你
Just came along for the ride.
鲍尔先生现在归我管
Mr. Bauer is here under my authority.
这么说他在这做的一切
Oh, so I can hold you responsible for anything
我都可以找你算账咯
He does while he's here.
我可有证人
I have a witness.
是的
Sure.
好吧
Okay.
请进
Come on in.
请随便
Please.
坐
Have a seat.
这应该是一次很有趣的谈话
This should be an interesting conversation.
多久没见了  杰克
How long's it been, Jack?
有几年了
Years.
参议院听证会的事怎么样了
How's the, uh... senate thing doing?
我听说反恐小组被撤销了
I hear they dismantled the ctu.
别告诉我
Don't tell me.
这是你的错  不是吗
It was your fault, wasn't it?
谢克特先生  我们不是来闲聊的
Mr.Schector, we're not here to make small talk.
我有几个问题
I have questions.
好的  我洗耳恭听
Well, you have my undivided attention.
托尼·阿尔梅达在哪
Where's Tony Almeida?
托尼·阿尔梅达
Tony Almeida?
在地下  我猜
In the ground, I suppose.
除非他被火化了
Unless he was cremated.
他不是在反恐小组时就挂了吗
Didn't he die at CTU a while back?
你与此事无关  加布里
You got an out here, gabe.
他们不是来找你的
They're not after you.
他们只是好奇
They're willing to accept that
托尼·阿尔梅达想用
You didn't know what Tony Almeida was going to do
你帮忙偷来的组件做什么
With the components that you helped him steal.
我可不知道有人偷了组件
Nobody I knew
就算是他们干的
Stole anything, and if they did,
我也毫不知情
I knew nothing about it.
事情比你想象的要严重得多  谢克特先生
This is far more serious than you know, Mr. Schector.
如果你帮我们找到阿尔梅达
If you help us find Almeida,
我可以保证你免于司法起诉
I can see to it that you're kept in the clear.
否则
Otherwise,
你会被认定为恐怖分子的同谋而遭起诉
You could be a co-conspirator to multiple terrorist acts.
我想我们的谈话结束了
No, well, I think this conversation is over.
我尽力诚实地回答你所有的问题
I tried to answer all your questions honestly,
但是  从现在起
But I think, from now on,
你只能和我的律师谈了
You can speak to my lawyers.
所以
So,
再见了  杰克
Good-bye, Jack.
我祝参议院好运  希望你完蛋
And good luck with the senate. hope they fry your ass.
阿里
Ari,
送客
Could you show these people to the door, please.
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure you want to play it like this?
我就是这么确定  杰克
Yeah, that's the way I want to play, Jack.
-把枪放下  -放下枪
Drop your weapon. drop it now!
好的  好的
Okay, okay, okay.
你们两个会进监狱的
You two are going to prison!
这是暴力行为
This was unprovoked! unprovoked!
你的人阿里先掏的抢  我有证人
Your man Ari was going for his gun-- I've got a witness.
为什么我们不再谈谈呢
Why don't we try having this conversation again.
托尼·阿尔梅达在哪
Where is Tony Almeida?
不
No.
我不和你谈
I'm not talking to you.
他在哪
Where is he?
托尼·阿尔梅达已经死了
Tony almeida's dead.
你想要我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
你来决定
This is your call.
好好修理他
Do whatever it takes.
这是违法的
This is against the law.
你不能这么做
You can't do this.
我很乐于这么做
I'm gonna enjoy this.
乐于做什么
Enjoy what?
好吧  好吧
All right, all right!
好吧
All right!
我会告诉你我知道的
I'll tell you what I know!
我可不想为了这事
There's no need
弄瞎我的眼睛
For me to lose my good looks over this.
很好
Okay.
上次我见到阿尔梅达
Last time I saw Almeida...
你没事吧
Are you all right?
没事
Yeah.
告诉你的人
Tell your men they've got a shooter
枪手在哥伦比亚楼顶 向南逃跑
On top of the Columbia building, heading south.
有人开枪  嫌犯中枪
Shots fired. suspects are down.
枪手在哥伦比亚楼顶
The shooter's on the roof of the columbia
向南逃跑
Building across the street.
封锁所有出口
Seal all exits.
喂
Yeah.
别插手这事  杰克
Get away from this, Jack.
托尼
Tony?
你和联邦调查局都无法阻止这事了
There's nothing you or the FBI can do about this.
放弃吧
Just stay away.
托尼  告诉我
Tony, just talk to me.
到底是怎么回事
What the hell's going...
托尼
Tony...
Tony!
谢克特办公室情况怎么样了
What's going on at Schector's office?
不知道  他们还没有汇报
I don't know. they haven't checked in yet.
GSA117号航班  我是东北三号
GSA 117, northeast three,
谨慎驾驶准备降落  方向肯尼迪国际机场
Descend pilot's discretion, direct jfk.
收到  东北三号  我们准备降落了
Northeast three, roger, we're starting our descent now.
GSA117号航班  降落保持高度2000
Gsa 117, descend and maintain 2,000,
4号右侧跑道降落
Expect holding runway four-right.
GSA117号航班  我没有收到回复
Gsa 117, I did not receive your read-back.
请确认  完毕
Acknowledge. over.
GSA117号航班  请确认
Gsa 117, acknowledge.
保尔森先生  我和GSA117号航班失去联系了
Mr. Paulson, I've lost comm with GSA 117.
尝试应急频道
Try the emergency channels.
我试了
I did.
还是没反应
Nothing.
我的线路没有任何问题
And there's no fault on my board.
我重新定向了两次
I redirected twice.
有人隔断了我们的联系
Something's interfering with our comm.
给联邦调查局打电话
Call back FBI!
说我们有一架波音767航班
Tell them we have a 767
被人劫持  失去控制
On approach no longer under our control!
-好的  长官  -GSA117号航班  请确认
Yes, sir. GSA 117, acknowledge.
GSA117号航班  我是东北三号
Gsa 117, this is northeast three.
请讲  航管局
Go ahead, air traffic control.
建议穿越高度7000  保持飞行1500
Advise passing 7,000, maintain 1,500.
前方报告会有少许乱流
Traffic ahead reporting moderate turbulence.
在那降落会更加平稳些
Should be a smoother ride for you down there.
收到  东北三号
Roger that, northeast three.
收到  东北三号  GSA117号航班
Understand, northeast three, gsa 117.
进入降落高度1500
Enter descent for 1,500.
好了
All right.
准备变更航线
Get ready to make the course change.
我们真要这么做吗
We're really taking this all the way.
你只需要按我说的做就行了
You just need to do exactly what I tell you to do.